{
    "id": "45164588c4bd4b0bad844b712df9e44e",
    "title": "Simple Present, Present Continuous Or Simple Future",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "b72b79b8efde4379977870de3151ed7f",
            "title": "Simple Present, Present Continuous Or Simple Future",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Dad ………………………. tomorrow.",
                    "description": "The present continuous is commonly used to talk about future events which have already been planned or decided.",
                    "answers": [
                        "leaves",
                        "will leave",
                        "is leaving"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The next term ………………………… on Monday.",
                    "description": "The simple present is used to talk about time tabled future events.",
                    "answers": [
                        "begins",
                        "will begin",
                        "is beginning"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ……………………… into a new home toward the end of this year.",
                    "description": "We use the simple future to talk about future events which are not already decided.",
                    "answers": [
                        "move",
                        "will probably move",
                        "am probably moving"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I think we ……………………….",
                    "description": "We use the simple future to talk about future events which are not already decided.",
                    "answers": [
                        "win",
                        "will win",
                        "are winning"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We ………………………….. to the countryside.",
                    "description": "The present continuous is commonly used to talk about future events which have already been planned or decided.",
                    "answers": [
                        "move",
                        "will move",
                        "are moving"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Rahul and Priya ………………………….. married next year.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "get",
                        "will get",
                        "are getting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you say that word again, I ……………………… you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hit",
                        "will hit",
                        "am hitting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………………… here until you return.",
                    "description": "Shall and will are common in offers, threats, promises and announcements of decisions.",
                    "answers": [
                        "wait",
                        "will wait",
                        "am waiting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………………………  I turn the heating on?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Will",
                        "Shall"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It ………………………….. in the evening.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "probably rain",
                        "will probably rain",
                        "is probably raining"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Look at the sky. It ………………………….. rain.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "go to",
                        "is going to",
                        "will go to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You …………………………… out what happened to her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will never find",
                        "are never finding",
                        "never find"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}